# Nanette Julius

Email: njulius89@gmail.com | Cell: (661) 993-7831 https://linkedin.com/in/nanette-julius/ | https://github.com/njulius89 www.nanettejulius.com

## **SUMMARY**

Creative problem-solving full stack web developer with the coordinating and interpersonal skills to match. I create user friendly, visually appealing applications that are functional and organized. Strong detail, communication and leadership skills developed through teaching experience.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Sass, Materialize, JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive Design, UX/UI Design, React.js, JSON, REST, AJAX, Firebase, Photoshop, WordPress, Chrome Dev Tools, GIT, GitHub, Node.js, Express, React Native, Google Firebase, SQL, Handlebars & MongoDB.

#### **EDUCATION**

University of California Los Angeles, Los Angeles, CA Certificate, Full Stack Web Development

2017

Cal State University Los Angeles, Los Angeles, CA B.A. Music

2013

### **APPLICATIONS BUILT**

## Swapr

- Full stack app for trading goods with other users nearby. Users can search for items within a set distance and arrange to meet and trade using the integrated chat feature.
- https://swapr-app.herokuapp.com/

## **EventStay**

- A frontend web app routing users to hotels near their desired events. Users can choose
  an event anywhere in the world and find the cheapest, highest rated hotels near it.
- http://nanettejulius.com/EventStay/

#### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

REX IT Inc. - Pasadena, CA

06/2016 to 07/2017

- Junior Web Developer
  - Designed clean, user-friendly, responsive websites/web applications
  - Ensured the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs
  - Developed new user-facing features
  - Helped other engineers with bug fixes and feature development
  - Application testing and improving test coverage

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

Gorman Learning Center – Santa Clarita, CA Performing Arts Program Director/ Music Teacher	08/2015 to 06/2017
Heritage Christian School - Granada Hills, CA Elementary Music Teacher/ Chapel Coordinator	07/2014 to 06/2015

Real Life Church - Santa Clarita, CA Music Department Coordinator

01/2012 to 6/2014